<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<title>Reuben's web page</title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org"/>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Updated the photo album section to display a slide show from my <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/screamingmonkey">flickr account</a>.


</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Updated the about me page to include the Brims 2010 paper. Also updated the broken miscellaneous page link.


</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>I have added a curious new section to this site. It is my brain dump exported from my org mode files. You can get a glimpse of stuff I read by looking at it <a href="org-index.html">here</a>

</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Added a recipe for Murgh Do Piaza <a href="Murgh2Piaza.html">here</a>.
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>Added pepper rasam recipe <a href="peprrasam.html">here</a>

</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Added a new script that compiles articles in to a nice format. Details and the source can be found on the "Scripts used to generate the pages
" <a href="page_script.html">page</a>.

 
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>As you can see I am beginning to change the typography on the website so as to make it more readable. I have changed the font to georgia that should be available on almost all computers. I have also changed the color of the font to black for higher contrast with the background. I have also set the line spacing to 1.5 em so as to give more space between lines. More changes coming soon!!!

</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Generating executables for lisp using SBCL</title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/compile_sbcl.html
"/>
<summary>
Added a page that describes how to compile lisp programs to binaries using sbcl <a href="compile_sbcl.html">here</a>.</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>

Major update, changed the webhosting service. Right now am hosting the site off Super Dimension Fortress.

Also I have changed the order of items on the Left menu.

</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Added recipe for rasam <a href="rasam.html">here</a>.

</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Added a page for the Indian national anthem <a href="anthem.html">here</a>.
Updated my resume.
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>

Make necessary entries as required by course 712 on the website. Also added my resume.
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Added a logo on the main page indicating the site's lisp heritage. The logo was designed by Conrad Barski, and it is available from <a href="http://www.lisperati.com/logo.html"> here</a>.
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Added a recipe for buffalo wings <a href="buffalo.html">here</a>.
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
This is quite a major update to the site. I've put up a photo album and a cooking section on the website. I've fixed the fonts. Made a whole lot of changes to the backend....etc...etc... This would be a major version release if this was software.
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Well...here it a change after ages...I hope I'm able to make an entry into this page more frequently. I have made some major changes, the backend HTML will be generated by a lisp script. I have also added a tutorial on ed. This is something that I wanted to do for quite a while, it can be found <a href="ed_tutorial.html">here</a>
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Yes, finally one more update. I have put up the handouts of the UNIX sessions which I had taken at office. They can be downloaded from <a href="unix_handouts.html">here.</a>
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Ah...This update was long overdue, I've put in a miscellaneous section.
I will be expanding this further. But for now I have only a section on 
the <a href="k1000_rally.html">Karnataka 1000 rally</a> for which I volunteered as a member of the 
communication group.
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
Added an <a href="aboutme.html">about me</a> page.
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary>
This page is new. I've added the script used to generate this page <a href="makenew.awk.txt">here</a>.
</summary>
</entry>
<entry>
<title></title>
<link href="http://rfcornel.freeshell.org/"/>
<summary></summary>
</entry>
</feed>
